[](https://www.critical-notes.com/) Critical Notes

Privacy Policy
==============

Critical Notes is website built and provided by [Loopwerk](https://www.loopwerk.io/), a company located in the Netherlands.

When you sign up using Sign In with Apple, we store only your first and last name as entered when you created this account. When you sign up using an emailed login link, we store only your email address. Any other information that you enter yourself when editing your profile, such as your name and your avatar, is stored.

* **When you choose to delete your account, all stored personal information is permanantly removed.**
* **We will never, ever, sell your data. We’re in the business of providing great digital roleplaying tools, not selling your data.**
* **We do not use any kind of ads, tracking, or cookies. You are not the product.**

Critical Notes uses **Plausible** for basic analytics. Plausible doesn’t use cookies and doesn’t track nor collect any personal data. Please refer to [their data policy](https://plausible.io/data-policy) for more information.

Critital Notes uses **Stripe** for payment processing. We don’t have access to your payment information such as credit card info or bank account details. Please refer to [their privacy policy](https://stripe.com/privacy) for more information.

If you want to delete your account you can do so from the Profile screen, at which point all personal information about you will be removed. User Generated Content (as in: content added by you to a Campaign), will not be removed when you delete your account.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.critical-notes.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Resources

### About

* [\[email protected\]](https://www.critical-notes.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)[](https://bsky.app/profile/critical-notes.com "Bluesky")[](https://dice.camp/@CriticalNotes "Mastodon")[](https://hachyderm.io/@kevinrenskers "Mastodon")

* Made with 🧡 using  
    [SvelteKit](https://kit.svelte.dev/) & [Django](https://www.djangoproject.com/).
